A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13 FA285
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Titles, 9
  - "Somatosensory Changes After Penetrating Brain Wounds in Man" - Editorial and Production, June 18, 1957-September 28, 1960 (Box 122, Folder 1391)
  - "Standard Classified Nomenclature of Disease", October 29, 1931-October 1, 1934 (Box 122, Folder 1392)
  - "State Health Departments of Massachusetts, Michigan and Ohio", April 26, 1929-November 18, 1930 (Box 122, Folder 1393)
  - "The Story of GAP", November 10, 1958-April 1, 1960 (Box 122, Folder 1394)
  - "The Student-Physician" - Correspondence, September 1, 1955-September 17, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 1395)
  - "The Student-Physician" - Distribution and Editorial, August 21, 1956-February 5, 1958 (Box 123, Folder 1396)
  - "The Student-Physician" - Production, October 21, 1953-October 8, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 1397)
  - "Studies in Schizophrenia" - Correspondence, February 27, 1953-March 31, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 1398)
  - "Studies in Schizophrenia" - Correspondence, February 27, 1953-March 31, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 1399)
  - "Studies in Schizophrenia" - Letters to Authors/Permission to Quote, October 1, 1953-November 20, 1953 (Box 123, Folder 1400)
  - "Studies in Schizophrenia" - Printing and Binding, March 17, 1953-September 28, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 1401)
  - "Studies in Schizophrenia" - Sales Promotion, July 15, 1953-March 31, 1955 (Box 123, Folder 1402)
  - "A Study of Rural Public Health Service", January 28, 1932-October 29, 1937 (Box 123, Folder 1403)
  - "Substitute Parents" - Correspondence, April 11, 1932-April 13, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 1404)
  - "Substitute Parents" - Printing, July 6, 1936-June 27, 1948 (Box 123, Folder 1405)
  - "Supervision in Public Health Nursing", November 27, 1937-May 8, 1967 (Box 124, Folder 1406)
  - "Survey of Public Health Nursing", May 15, 1931-December 12, 1933 (Box 124, Folder 1407)
  - "Synovial Fluid Changes in Joint Disease" - Correspondence and Permission to Quote, October 18, 1951-March 31, 1966 (Box 124, Folder 1408)
  - "Synovial Fluid Changes in Joint Disease" - Printing and Sales Promotion, November 1, 1951-January 7, 1957 (Box 124, Folder 1409)
  - "Teachers and Behavior Problems" - Correspondence, September 10, 1937-October 2, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 1410)
  - "Teachers and Behavior Problems" - Printing, March 26, 1938-March 12, 1951 (Box 124, Folder 1411)
  - "Teaching and Learning in Medical Schools" - Correspondence and Distribution, December 16, 1958-August 30, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 1412)
  - "Teaching and Learning in Medical Schools" - Editorial and Production, September 1, 1960-June 24, 1964 (Box 124, Folder 1413)
  - "Teaching Comprehensive Medical Care" - Correspondence, February 1, 1956-September 7, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 1414)
  - "Teaching Comprehensive Medical Care" - Correspondence, February 1, 1956-September 7, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 1415)
  - "Teaching Comprehensive Medical Care" - Correspondence, February 1, 1956-September 7, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 1416)
  - "Teaching Comprehensive Medical Care" - Correspondence-Ward Darley, January 17, 1958-January 11, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1417)
  - "Teaching Comprehensive Medical Care" - Distribution, March 3, 1959-March 14, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 1418)
  - "Teaching Comprehensive Medical Care" - Editorial, December 2, 1957-September 9, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 1419)
  - "Teaching Comprehensive Medical Care" - Permission to Quote and Production, December 27, 1957-April 25, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 1420)
  - "Teaching Health in Fargo", 1929-1932, 1941 (Box 125, Folder 1421)
  - "Teaching Preventive Medicine to Medical Students", January 8, 1941-May 1, 1944 (Box 125, Folder 1422)
  - "Teaching Psychotherapeutic Medicine" - Correspondence and Distribution, May 7, 1946-February 28, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 1423)
  - "Teaching Psychotherapeutic Medicine" - Printing, April 23, 1947-May 31, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 1424)
  - "Ten Years of Rural Health Work" - Correspondence and Printing, October 13, 1934-December 3, 1940 (Box 126, Folder 1425)
  - Testimonials, January 20, 1954-February 26, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 1426)
  - "These Two Strange Years", October 22, 1941-April 19, 1944 (Box 126, Folder 1427)
  - "Thinking and Psychotherapy" - Correspondence, February 3, 1959-February 21, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 1428)
  - "Thinking and Psychotherapy" - Distribution/Editorial, March 12, 1959-February 14, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 1429)
  - "Thinking and Psychotherapy" - Permission to Quote and Production, April 6, 1960-June 16, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 1430)
  - "Three Problem Children", 1927, 1970 (Box 126, Folder 1431)
  - "Training in Psychiatric Social Work", 1933-1937, 1949 (Box 126, Folder 1432)
  - Travel Expense Booklets, March 22, 1954-August 2, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 1433)
  - "Treatment of Behavior Disorder Following Encephalitis", September 16, 1929-January 14, 1936 (Box 126, Folder 1434)
  - "Trends in Medical Education" - Correspondence and Distribution, March 8, 1948-October 16, 1951 (Box 126, Folder 1435)
  - "Trends in Medical Education" - Printing, March 9, 1949-December 8, 1950 (Box 126, Folder 1436)
  - "Tuberculosis in White and Negro Children" - Correspondence, February 25, 1948-June 10, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 1437)
  - "Tuberculosis in White and Negro Children" - Distribution and Editorial, October 4, 1954-May 1, 1958 (Box 127, Folder 1438)
  - "Tuberculosis in White and Negro Children" - Production, November 5, 1956-March 31, 1958 (Box 127, Folder 1439)
  - "Tutoring as Therapy" - Correspondence, January 31, 1942-February 25, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 1440)
  - "Tutoring as Therapy" - Distribution and Printing, April 18, 1946-December 16, 1958 (Box 127, Folder 1441)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Correspondence - General, April 1, 1939-December 16, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1442)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Correspondence - General, April 1, 1939-December 16, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1443)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Correspondence - General, April 1, 1939-December 16, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1444)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Correspondence (P-S), May 5, 1949-July 30, 1951 (Box 128, Folder 1445)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Disguises, January 1, 1950-January 5, 1952 (Box 128, Folder 1446)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Distribution, November 28, 1949-February 13, 1953 (Box 128, Folder 1447)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Editorial, November 23, 1949-February 21, 1950 (Box 128, Folder 1448)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Printing, June 15, 1949-August 31, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 1449)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency" - Sales Promotion, March 22, 1949-May 8, 1952 (Box 128, Folder 1450)
  - "Visiting Teacher At Work", April 8, 1929-October 30, 1941 (Box 128, Folder 1451)
  - "Visual Field Defects After Penetrating Missile Wounds of the Brain" - Correspondence and Distribution, August 31, 1956-September 19, 1961 (Box 128, Folder 1452)
  - "Visual Field Defects After Penetrating Missile Wounds of the Brain" - Editorial and Production, June 18, 1958-November 1, 1960 (Box 128, Folder 1453)
  - "Vocational Rehabilitation of Psychiatric Patients", March 16, 1949-May 8, 1952 (Box 129, Folder 1454)
  - "Vocational Services for Psychiatric Clinic Patients", February 14, 1951-December 1, 1955 (Box 129, Folder 1455)
  - "The War and Mental Health in England", October 15, 1943-June 28, 1949 (Box 129, Folder 1456)
  - "Ways to Community Health Education" - Correspondence - Expenses/General, January 8, 1935-July 11, 1951 (Box 129, Folder 1457)
  - "Ways to Community Health Education" - Correspondence - Printing, 1940-1950, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 1458)
  - "Ways to Community Health Education" - Correspondence - Publications Committee, January 2, 1936-December 20, 1939 (Box 129, Folder 1459)
  - "Ways to Community Health Education" - Permission to Quote (A-L), January 19, 1937-October 30, 1939 (Box 129, Folder 1460)
  - "Ways to Community Health Education" - Permission to Quote (M-Y), June 21, 1937-October 19, 1939 (Box 129, Folder 1461)
  - "Ways to Community Health Education" - Printing, September 24, 1937-February 28, 1952 (Box 130, Folder 1462)
  - "Widening Horizons in Medical Education", December 17, 1946-June 24, 1957 (Box 130, Folder 1463)
- Miscellaneous, 10
  - Commonwealth Fund Book Program (Report to the Board of Directors by Carleton B. Chapman), November 8, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 1464)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (B-S), February 26, 1988-July 12, 1989 (Box 130, Folder 1465)
  - Weinerman, E. Richard (Adm-H File), July 20, 1967-October 23, 1970 (Box 130, Folder 1466)
  - Werkman, Sidney L. - "Role of Psychiatry in Medical Education", February 4, 1964-April 4, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1467)
  - Wood, Harrison F., January 12, 1967-September 29, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1468)
- Authors Files, 11
  - Altschule, Mark D. - Physiological Studies of Pineal Gland - 1-36, 1952-1961 (Box 131, Folder 1469)
  - Altschule, Mark D. - Physiological Studies of Pineal Gland - 37-46, 1952-1961 (Box 131, Folder 1470)
  - California Institute of Technology -Research in Chemistry and Biology, 1956, 1962 (Box 131, Folder 1471)
  - Cowles and Rimoldi - Medical Ability and Proficiency, 1951-1963 (Box 131, Folder 1472)
  - Dykman, R. - Neural Influences on Kidney Function, 1956-1966 (Box 131, Folder 1473)
  - Gersh, Isadore - Histochemical Studies of the Submicroscopic Organization of Cells and of Extra Cellular Substances - 1-17, 1948-1961 (Box 132, Folder 1474)
  - Gersh, Isadore - Histochemical Studies of the Submicroscopic Organization of Cells and of Extra Cellular Substances - 18-40, 1959-1962 (Box 131, Folder 1475)
  - Gersh, Isadore - Book - Biological Applications of Freezing and Drying - R.J.C. Harris, 1954 (Box 132, Folder 1476)
  - Gersh, Isadore - Book - Veterans Administration: Research in Aging, 1959 (Box 132, Folder 1477)
  - Hamilton, Leonard - Nucleic Acids Nucleoproteins - 1-10, 1955-1963 (Box 132, Folder 1478)
  - Hamilton, Leonard - Nucleic Acids Nucleoproteins - 11-29, 1955-1963 (Box 132, Folder 1479)
  - Hechter, Oscar - Steroids - 1-13, 1953-1963 (Box 133, Folder 1480)
  - Hechter, Oscar - Steroids - 14-25, 1953-1963 (Box 133, Folder 1481)
  - Hechter, Oscar - Steroids - 26-43, 1953-1963 (Box 133, Folder 1482)
  - Hume, David - Control of Pituitary Function, 1949-1962 (Box 133, Folder 1483)
  - Kluver, and Others - Porphyrins - 1-14, 1930-1958 (Box 133, Folder 1484)
  - Kluver, and Others - Porphyrins - 15-24, 1930-1958 (Box 133, Folder 1485)
  - Kluver, and Others - Porphyrins - 25-42, 1930-1958 (Box 134, Folder 1486)
  - Lief, H. - Medical Students and Their Adaptational Problems, 1956-1957 (Box 134, Folder 1487)
    - Richards and Others - Respiratory Physiology
      - 1 - 15, 1932- 1944 (Box 135, Folder 1492)
      - 16 - 23, 1932-1944 (Box 135, Folder 1493)
      - 24 - 30a, 1932-1944 (Box 135, Folder 1494)
      - 31 - 39, 1945-1957 (Box 135, Folder 1495)
      - 40 - 55, 1945-1957 (Box 135, Folder 1496)
      - 56 - 65, 1945-1957 (Box 135, Folder 1497)
  - Lurie, Max B. and Others - Study of Constitutional Factors in Resistance to Tuberculosis - 1-6, 1939-1945 (Box 134, Folder 1488)
  - Lurie, Max B. and Others - Study of Constitutional Factors in Resistance to Tuberculosis - 1- 31, 1946-1956 (Box 134, Folder 1489)
  - Puck, Theodore - Biophysics Research - 1-17, 1953-1966 (Box 134, Folder 1490)
  - Puck, Theodore - Biophysics Research - 18-42, 1953-1966 (Box 134, Folder 1491)
  - Richards and Others - Respiratory Physiology - 1-30A, 1932-1944 (Box 135, Folder 1492-1494)
  - Richards and Others - Respiratory Physiology - 31-65, 1945-1957 (Box 135, Folder 1495-1497)
  - Sturgis, S. - Psychiatric Research in Gynecology, 1952-1962 (Box 135, Folder 1498)
  - Szent - Gyorgyi - Chemical Mechanism of Introcellular Energy Transmission, 1954-1963 (Box 136, Folder 1499-1501)
  - Talbot, Nathan B. and Others - Endocrinological Study - 1-21, 1941-1948 (Box 136, Folder 1502)
  - Talbot, Nathan B. and Others - Endocrinological Study - 22-38, 1941-1948 (Box 136, Folder 1503)
  - Talbot, Nathan B. and Others - Endocrinological Study - 39-59, 1950-1958 (Box 136, Folder 1504)
  - Talbot, Nathan B. and Others - Patient Management - 1-4, 1959-1962 (Box 136, Folder 1505)
  - Teuber, Hans - Lucas - Cerebral Function, 1948-1960 (Box 137, Folder 1506-1509)
  - Washburn and Others - Growth and Development Study, 1934-1945 (Box 138, Folder 1510-1513)
  - Washburn and Others - Growth and Development Study, 1946-1957 (Box 138, Folder 1514-1516)
  - Washburn and Others - Growth and Development Study, 1946-1962 (Box 139, Folder 1517)
  - Wilson, Mary G. and Others - Study of Rheumatic Fever, 1920-1962 (Box 139, Folder 1518-1520)
  - Worthington, C. - Vascular Studies for the Pituitary Gland, 1955, 1966 (Box 139, Folder 1521)